byjoomla.com 2010-10-30

# ByJoomla - Privacy Policy

**Byjoomla.com - Privacy Policy** are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Following outlines our continued support for the responsible management of consumer information. 

### Consumer Information

We do not track, collect or distribute personal information about visitors of our website. We only tracks information about the visits to our web sites. For example, we compile statistics that show the daily number of visitors to our sites, the daily requests we receive for particular files on our web sites, and what countries those requests come from. These aggregated statistics are used to better provide services to the public and may also be provided to others, but again, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information. However, if you decided to register on our website and forum your personal information required by register process will be added to our user database. If at any time you change your mind and would like to be removed from our user database we claims to delete all your personal data. 

### No Release/Share/Sell of Information

Your personal information will not be released to third parties and shared among other users except to further the purpose for which you had provided the information, such as making specific requests for information, or if you request that your email be forwarded. There are no other circumstances under which we will provide or sell personal information to third parties. 

### No Sell of User List

We do not sell user list of our users to any third party company for any further purposes. All information about our users are stored in the password protected database installed in secure server hosting machine.
